Emmet Family
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
Sep 20, [1925] - To: Jane - From: Posie - Subjects: Jank--children's name for Bobby Sherwood; luncheons with Matilda Brownell, Mrs. Montgomery Sears, Allie Haughton, and Mary Haydon; Posie and Arthur Sr. will live at 26 E 63rd in winter
Dec 7, [1925] - To: Jane - From: Lydia - Subject: Susie in London; Katy expecting; the Sargent exhibition in Boston; Damrosch concert; little Mary Sherwood
Dec 7, 1925 - To: Jane - From: Posie (at Hotel Leonori. New York) - Subjects: Posie wants photo of Wilfrid's painting of Jane; Posie's drawings of Arsie and Ginny; Bobby Sherwood has water on the knee; Anita von Hemert's wedding; Elsie expecting; Phil at Fort Riley; Posie to Rye to do watercolor of Beulah and portrait of John Patten; Sargent exhibition; Flo's son Buddy flouncing about in London
Jan 28, [1926?]To:Jane - From: Lydia - Subjects: Lydia to Susie's; Lydia painted Hazard boys; the Lunts in The Goat Song; Susie and Pablo concerts in Buffalo and DC; Ros and Lybba to Beaux Arts Ball (Lybba as Pompadour); Priscilla's wedding; Toscanini; Sargent exhibition at Met half the size as at Boston
Jan 31, 1926 - To: Jane - From: Posie (at Hotel Leonori, New York) - Subject: 50th anniversary of Lampoon next week--Lampoon started in Arthur Sr.'s room at college; Ros to Beaux Arts Ball with Lybba and Eddie; catalog of Sargent exhibition; Rockefeller portraits; Bea Lillie, Gertie Lawrence, Noel Coward
Jan 31, 1926 - To: Lydia - From: Lydia Maxwell - Subject: Academy doesn't want portrait
May 14, [1926] - To: Arthur - From: Posie - Subject: the Astaires in Lady Be Good; Posie could hear
May 17, 1926 - To: Lydia - From: Posie (68 Oakley St., London) - Subjects: Lydia ill; London transit strike; Grantchester is 2 mi. from Cambridge; Roger Quilter; Mark Raphael
May 19, [1926] - To: Arthur - From: Posie (in London) - Subjects: Ros' golf partner was Joy Wynne; Mrs. Ralph Burton? (actress)
May 21, [1926] - To: Arthur - From: Posie (in London) - Subjects: Lord Denbigh married Kitty (after living with her for 3 years); His sister is Lady Winifred Eleves
May 25, 1926 - To: Arthur - From: Posie (in Chichester) - Subject: Roger Quilter
Jun 7, 1926 - To: Ros - From: Posie (aboard R.M.S. Samaria) - Subjects: voyage home; Ros stays in England; Posie to paint the Gray child
Nov 18, 1926 - To: Ros - From: Bartow Hall - Subject: thanks for painting
[Nov/Dec 1926] - To: Jane? - From: Lydia - Subjects: Helen Hastings loves Wilfrid's paintings; Lynn Fontanne in Pygmalion; Alfred in a Sidney Howard play with Clare Eames; Jane Cowl in Bobby Sherwood's play Road to Rome
[1926] - To: Bobby Sherwood - From: Edward Sheldon (copy written by Posie) - Subject: Sheldon liked reading Bobby's play; Jane Cowl; Doris Keane
Dec 26, 1926 - To: Ros - From: William Proctor - Subject: thanks for portrait of children
Dec 28, 1926 - To: Lydia - From: Phil - Subject: painting of Cynthia by Cecilia Beaux
Feb 11, 1927 - To: Lydia - From: Frances C. White - Subject: clipping re: Martha van Rensselaer
Mar 23, 1927 - To: Lydia - From: Matilda (Brownell) - Subject: saw portrait of the three girls at the Academy
May 29, 1927 - To: Jane - From: Lydia - Subjects: Hallie Greene's grandson; Howard Potter's daughter married Kenyon Cox's son; Bay's operation; Bill Rand's accident
Sep 20, 1927 - To: Ros - From: Elton Hoyt (and Cornelia) - Subject: wants her to paint Betty Johnson
Oct 3, 1927 - To: Ros - From: John T. Blossom - Subject: played Bud Wick and Charlie Vilas
Dec 6, 1927 - To: Lydia - From: Posie (at Fort Bliss, Texas) - Subject: start home Monday via New Orleans; Bobby's sinus problems; Phil's operation
[1928] - To: Lydia - From: Posie - Subjects: Bobby Sherwood's Hannibal;portrait of Merivale
Jan 17, [1928] - To: Jane - From: Lydia - Subjects: Bobby Sherwood; Road to Rome with Jane Cowl and Merivale; Pablo to lead Boston orchestra next year; Alec James
Feb 3, [1928] - To: Jane - From: Lydia - Subjects: Lydia's description of Road to Rome; Alexander Woollcott; Clare Eames; Sidney Howard; the Lunts; Pablo; Bay and Leslie's new apartment; Toscanini
Feb 14, [1928] - To: Jane - From: Lydia - Subjects: the Lunts; Susie and Pablo; Road to Rome; Juliet Hamilton; Esther Kirkland; Joyce Carey; Stokowski awful
Mar 31, [1928] - To: Jane - From: Lydia - Subjects: tea for the Astors; Road to Rome popular; Posie paints Merivale and Cowl; Clare Eames; Furtwangler
Apr 15, [1928] - To: Jane - From: Posie - Subjects: Jane's picture in the Royal Academy; Jane's former digs on 67th St.; Geoffrey Kerr does card tricks; Phil to go to Walter Reed; Anne Choate; Bill's medal from DC
Apr 21, 1928 - To: Lydia - From: Mrs. George Douglas - Subjects: Freer collection; thanks for portrait of Eleanor
May 8, [1928] - To: Jane - From: Posie - Subjects: Jane has measles; Arthur Sr. has a nurse
May 14, 1928 - To: Jane - From: Posie - Subjects: Jane's illness; Bobby Sherwood's sinus; Road to Rome opens in London; Ros to Cleveland; Cynthia's new house at St. James
May 21, [1928] - To: Jane - From: Posie - Subjects: Dev had a fall; Cynthia to St. James
[May 28, 1928] - To: Jane - From: Posie - Subjects: Isobel Jeans; Arthur Sr. very ill
Jun 4, 1928 - To: Jane - From: Lydia Emmet Sherwood - Subjects: Arthur Sherwood Sr. died June 3; she met Dennis King from D'Artagnan; (drawing of his dressing room)
Jun 12, 1928 - To: Jane - From: Posie - Subject: failure of Road to Rome
Jul 13, 1928 - To: Jane - From: Lydia Emmet Sherwood - Subject: Jane in Cornwall
Aug 17, [1928] - To: Jane - From: Posie - Subjects: Lybba and the little boys; Posie to draw Mary Sherwood's grandfather; Road to Rome a success in California-- Jane Cowl; Posie to move to Lexington and 71st, opposite Bob's house; Barb and Titus Rand; Lydia paints Philby
Sep 25, [1928?] - To: Jane - From: Lydia - Subjects: Lydia paints Kitty Hunnewell, Copley's great-granddaughter; Mary Hale to dinner--her Sargent article; Lydia bought a house--between 70th and 71st, opposite Cynthia's; Nick Biddle's wedding; Mrs. Coolidge's disinterest in art; if Pablo asks, Susie will go back; opening of Waterloo Bridge--Glenn Hunter'sdissipation worries June Walker
Nov 21, [1928] - To: Jane - From: Lydia - Subjects: Matilda (Brownell); Posie at Hotel Leonori; Mrs. Russell Wheeler; Jim Townsend's operation; Posie knocked down by dog
Nov 28, 1928 - To: Lydia - From: Sallie Miller Smith - Subject: portrait of Charles and Jack Durfee
Jan 31, 1929 - To: Lydia - From: Cornelia Vanderbilt - Subject: thanks for portrait of Ann
Mar 24, [1929] - To: Jane - From: Lydia - Subjects: Susie's tea party; Zeb sick; Susie and Pablo; Kate Foote; O'Neill's play Street Scene
Apr [1929] - To: Jane - From: Lydia - Subjects: Dick's operation; hopeBobby Sherwood is ok
Apr 4, 1929 - To: Jane - From: Lydia Emmet Sherwood - Subjects: Uncle Gabby's shipboard letter; Bobby Sherwood's birthday; Lawrence Tibbett; the Opera house to be razed; (drawing of flowerpot)
Apr 8, 1929 - To: Lydia - From: Francis Randolph - Subject: thanks for portrait
Apr 12, 1929 - To: Jane - From: Posie - Subjects: Posie tries for exhibition at Knoedlers; Bay at Durand-Ruel; Bobby Sherwood is literary critic for Scribner's; Road to Rome; Lybba and Eddie Morgan; Frances Starr (actress); Ros with Beatrice Renwick
Apr 20, 1929 - To: Lydia - From: James Thomson - Subject: thanks for portraits
Apr 29, 1929 - To: Jane - From: Lydia - Subjects: Tappy's wedding; Mrs. Schley's portrait; Cynthia abroad next winter; Nite expecting; Bobby and Mary Sherwood's Surrey house; John Powell (musician); Susie and Pablo fight; Hilda's death
May 12, [1929] - To: Jane - From: Lydia Emmet Sherwood - Subject: Bobby and Mary Sherwood settled at Poleshot Farm
May 26, [1929] - To: Jane - From: Posie - Subjects: Bobby Sherwood on holiday in England; Mrs. Duryea abroad; Johnny Dodge; Genevieve Forbes; Susie lives with Lydia for now but hasn't left Pablo
Jun 6, 1929 - To: Lydia - From: Jane - Subjects: the Lunts in Caprice; Jung getting Mary Foote's nerves in shape; Mary Foote saw Pablo; Rob and Beulah in London
Jun 12, [1929] - To: Lydia - From: Jane - Subject: Caprice; Percy Grainger's wife; Bessie White motoring with Matilda Brownell; Mr. Baring, Maud's widower, is now Lord Ravenstoke
Jun 13, [1929] - To: Lydia - From: Jane - Subjects: the Lunts; Yvonne Printemps
Jul 1, 1929 - To: Lydia - From: William Wickham Hoffman - Subject: thanks for portrait
Jul 3, 1929 - To: Jane - From: Lydia - Subjects: Nite's child born--Mary Bartow Hall; Hetty's anniversary July 28; Margaret Anglin (actress)
Aug 4, [1929] - To: Jane - From: Lydia - Subjects: Ferber's Royal Family; Posie's horrible cook; Susie and Louis back from Nassau; Susie and Pablo final arraignment; Bessie Hitchcock (Fiske)
Aug 29, 1929 - To: Lydia - From: Lydia Emmet Sherwood - Subject: European trip
Sep 1, 1929 - To: Jane - From: Lydia - Subject: Dick's death Aug 28
Sep 2, 1929 - To: Jane - From: Posie - Subjects: Dick's last days; Bobby's book for Scribner's; picture exhibition opens next Saturday
Sep 7, 1929 - To: Lydia - From: Lydia Emmet Sherwood - Subjects: her mother back from Europe
Sep 22, [1929] - To: Jane - From: Lydia - Subjects: Bobby and Mary Sherwood's new car; Miss Farrington wants to be an artist; art awards; Lydia just finished portrait of John Runnels (Alice James' nephew)
Oct 25, 1929 - To: Jane - From: Posie - Subjects: Posie in Virginia and DC a week ago- saw Phil in hospital; watercolor of Ann for Auerbach's Christmas
[1929] - To: Lydia - From: Posie - Subjects: picture of Mrs. Jordan on the ship; Great Enton; Bobby's movie work; Cynthia in Berkeley Square; Sydney Howard says Cynthia was good in Declasse--Clare Eames had the part first; Ethel Barrymore
Nov 6, 1929 - To: Jane - From: Lydia - Subject: Susie wants marriage with Pablo
Nov 8, [1929] - To: Posie - From: Jane - Subjects: Posie's Virginia trip; Eliza Wedgewood; Wilfrid painting Nancy Astor and her daughter Phyllis; Jane painting Thomas Arnold Thwaite; Bay's portrait of Bill; Violet (Sargent) Ormond ill with shingles; the Indian question--Baldwin, Ramsay MacDonald, Lloyd George
[Nov 1929] - To: Lydia - From: Jerome Milkman - Subject: request for a letter for his collection
Nov 14, 1929 - To: Jane - From: Lydia Emmet - Subjects: Buddy Cross and Angus SherwoodWilson; the play Journey's End; Waterloo Bridge with Glenn Hunter and June Walker opens in Boston on Thursday; (drawing of Brearly School)
Nov 16, 1929 - To: Jane - From: Posie - Subjects: Winthrop Ames to produce Marching As to War; Winchel Smith produced Waterloo Bridge; Elsie's baby due Feb 1; Lybba has Manship's studio on 72nd St. with Ros and Dorothy Kane
Dec 1, [1929?] - To: Posie - From: Phil - Subject: at Walter Reed hospital
Dec 1, 1929 - To: Jane - From: Lydia - Subjects: Posie's 75th birthday party; finished Mr. Griswold; Susie and Pablo not sailing together; June Walker is inadequate in role
Dec 5, [1929] - To: Jane - From: Lydia (in Boston) - Subject: reception of Waterloo Bridge
Dec 5, 1929 - To: Jane - From: Lydia - Subjects: studio quest; Lydia's architect, Harry Polhemns; Lybba and Eddie away; Maria Whitehead; Waterloo Bridge to New York after Christmas; where's Susie; (drawing of studio window)
Dec 6, 1929 - To: Lydia - From: Virginia Gerson - Subject: portrait of Philby and Anita
Dec 6, [1929] - To: Lydia - From: Eleanor Ferguson - Subject: little Henry's portrait
Dec 23, 1929 - To: Jane - From: Posie - Subject: Waterloo Bridge; Geoffrey Kerr is June Walker's husband; Phil glad to be away from hospital
Dec 26, [1929] - To: Lydia - From: Eliza Wedgewood - Subject: holiday greetings
Jan 1, 1930 - To: Lydia - From: Mag - Subjects: thanks for portrait of boy; Geraldine Millet is here
Jan 7, 1930 - To: Lydia - From: Emily G. Whitlock - Subject: loves the picture
Jan 13, 1930 - To: Lydia - From: Paul Cravath - Subject: Buster's portrait
Jan 16, 1930 - To: Lydia - From: Phil - Subject: the critics "sent Bob to bed"
Feb 16, 1930 - To: Lydia - From: Gabrielle (in French) - Subject: portrait of Philby
Mar 31, 1930 - To: Lydia - From: J. Millard Curry - Subject: portrait of Philby
Apr 14, 1930 - To: Jane - From: Lydia - Subjects: Lydia painted two Whitney girls; Jeanne Eagles movie The Letter; Pablo in Italy; Bay at Durand-Ruel; Royal Cortissoz
May 21, 1930 - To: Lydia - From: John W. Mariner - Subject: Deirdre's portrait
[1930?] - To: "Old Man" - From: Posie (in Chicago) - Subjects: Bill's Mercury turbine invention; Taintor family to Santa Barbara for winter
May 23, 1930 - To: Jane - From: Posie - Subjects: Bob and Mary Sherwood; Bill discussed his Mercury turbine; Mariana van Rensselaer in Alice Hamilton's house
Jun 26, 1930 - To: Lydia - From: Jane - Subjects: read clippings about Toscanini at Queen's Hall; sorry about Mary's grandmother; Wilfrid's exhibition; reception of Bobby's play in London; comment on modern paintings
Jun 29, [1930] - To: Jane - From: Lydia - Subjects: Billy Floyd has cancer--worked with Lydia 15 years; Lydia says she never could've gotten into 535 Park Avenue without (Joe?) Brisache; Dozia needs eye operation in DC; Willy and Alida at studio; June Walker and Geoffrey Kerr in Admirable Creighton
Jul 6, [1930] - To: Jane - From: Posie - Subjects: Connie Brandon; Hetty's baby; Bobby Sherwood and Garrick Club- Geoffrey Kerr and June Walker in Admirable Creighton; June Walker to Hollywood for a movie; Bill Tilden in the papers; Ellen Taintor's wedding; Posie paints Mrs. Rice
Jul 25, 1930 - To: Jane - From: Lydia - Subjects: Lydia did pastels at Mrs. Rice's; Archie took Jeanne Millet to dance; Arthur Jr.'s disappointing news; Road to Rome in Newport
Jul 28, 1930 - To: Jane - From: Lydia Emmet Sherwood - Subject: Miss Poteet; Phil's family in Kent house
Aug 3, [1930?] - To: Jane - From: Lydia - Subjects: Jane's trip to US in winter?; Susie without Pablo; excitement over 214--no sun in 535 Park Avenue; Lydia will paint
May Field; met Billy Floyd's son; Phil recovering from operations; saw Romeo and Juliet with Edith Barrett (Lawrence Barrett's granddaughter), Alexander Knox as Romeo, and Hale as Mercutio
Sep 9, [1930] - To: Jane - From: Posie - Subjects: Lydia paints Field girl; Metcalfes in Nassau; Bobby Sherwood's bad teeth; play ends, film begins
Sep 14, [1930?] - To: Lydia - From: Jane (chez Bellah and Auguste, in Le Havre) - Subjects: Jane left Inglewidden a week ago, will go to Cannes; Lydia moves into 214 E 70th St.; Lydia saw Romeo and Juliet with Susie
Sep 20, [1930] - To: Jane - From: Lydia - Subjects: Lydia moving from 535 to 214 E 70 St.; finished
May Field; in exhibition with "modern horrors"; no word from Pablo but letters from Maria Casals; saw Edith Barrett in Romeo and Juliet; Mousie Garrett's wedding to Tom Hughes; Jane goes to France
Nov 30, [1930?] - To: Jane - From: Nite - Subjects: Nite and Bartow have been in Colorado; Jane and Wilfrid
May visit U.S. end of next summer?; Bobby Sherwood's play This is New York opened
Dec 1, 1930 - To: Jane - From: Posie - Subjects: Bobby's play a hit; Marching As to War to be produced sometime; Aveline took home Lois Moran, the young leading lady who has been in movies, but this is her first play--Hopkins will feature her; Phil's family in new house
Dec 10, 1930 - To: Jane - From: Posie - Subjects: Lydia's place is nice with things from 535; Eddie Morgan wants divorce from Lybba who
May live at her studio; Bobby's play not a big hit--Hopkins is the producer; engagement of Polly Damrosch and Sidney Howard (his first wife Clare Eames died recently); Temple and Alida to Rome
Dec 15, [1930] - To: Jane - From: Lydia - Subjects: repaint Anne Hart?; Lydia's tooth pulled; Joe Brisache; Olin Downes; Susie to go to Florida on 20th; Lybba begged to be taken in; June Walker's day bed; Archer engaged to Polish princess Joya; Leslie had another face operation; Lunts in Elizabeth and Essex and rehearse Much Ado
[1931] - To: Jane - From: Lydia - Subjects: Floyd's death; Susie and Pablo; Eddie and Lybba; Jane's room is ready; Mrs. Scott died; Eliza liked Wilfrid's portrait
Jan 3, 1931 - To: Jane - From: Posie - Subjects: Bob and Mary Sherwood; Mrs. Kermit Roosevelt; Bill will finish the Mercury boiler and become a consulting engineer only; movie rights to play sold to Paramount; Bobby Sherwood's novel The Virtuous Knight; The Queen's Husband is now a movie and is Le Roi S'Ennuie in France, directed by Gloria Swanson's husband
Jan 6, 1931 - To: Lydia - From: Mrs. J. B. Russell (Lucille Harvey Russell) - Subject: thesis
Jan 8, 1931 - To: Jane - From: Lydia - Subjects: Lydia finished portrait of Groton boy; Lulu Emmet died; Geoffrey Kerr; Bobby and little Mary
Jan 12, 1931 - To: Posey - From: Cecilia Beaux - Subject: Beaux' book
Jan 26, 1931 - To: Jane - From: Posie - Subjects: is Bobby Marsh well?; Geoffrey Kerr and June Walker in guild play Green Grow the Lilacs in DC; Bobby's play can't tour--Ziegfield, Marilyn Miller, and the Astaires closed too; book The Virtuous Knight; Bobby Sherwood to California in April; Arthur Jr. lost job at Radio Corp. of America and couldn't go to RKO
Feb 17, [1931] - To: Jane - From: Posie (142 E 71st) - Subject: Posie to paint Winthrop Aldrich's boy; sorry about Louis--give him and Dinah love; Lydia at after-theater party with the Lunts, Bob and Mary and June Walker; The Virtuous Knight; Barry Jones and Maurice Colbourne in Shaw's Apple Cart
Feb 28, [1931] - To: Jane - From: Lydia - Subjects: Lydia loves her house; the Lunts were out West last summer; Bay paints Bobby Sherwood
Mar 20, 1931 - To: Lydia - From: Katharine Barney - Subject: thanks for portrait
Apr 6, 1931 - To: Lydia - From: Josephine Barran - Subject: thanks for portrait
Apr 17, [1931] - To: Jane - From: Posie - Subjects: Posie found apartment at Lexington and 69th; Posie painted Winthrop Aldrich boy; Lydia painted old Mr. Van Cl____; Florence buying house next to Lydia's- Bancel (Louis Bancel LaFarge) is architect to convert property
May 7, 1931 - To: Lydia - From: Jane - Subject: Tristan at opera with Fuda Leider singing; saw Die Fledermaus with Roger Quilter, the Marks, and Barbara; Wilfrid sold a piece from the Royal Academy exhibition; Florence and Langers (Frederic E. Langermann); the John Russell Popes want Wilfrid to paint their daughter; Wilfrid to paint Ursula Lawley (now Lady Wraxall)
May 7, 1931 - To: Lydia - From: Mrs. George Douglas(Bessie) - Subject: love portrait of Eleanor
May 15, 1931 - To: Jane - From: Posie - Subjects: Florence back and buying a house; Posie will live in lower apartment after Christmas; Helen Gibson (DeWolf's wife) may rent Posie's apt.; surprise party at Lybba's for Ros; Leslie has pneumonia; Terrence says Henrietta has cancer, she's 78; Bobby Sherwood's new play Reunion in Vienna (originally Celebration), Alfred Lunt plays the archduke; June Walker expecting in October, Geoffrey in talkies
May 16, [1931] - To: Jane - From: Lydia - Subjects: Schley boys portrait; Cartlidge painting; Bay; Ros birthday party; Jack Pope wants daughter's portrait; Posie's cataracts; Reunion in Vienna; Bobby Sherwood family in California
May 27, [1931] - To: Lydia - From: Jane - Subjects: Wilfrid painted the Pope child and entered Lybba's portrait in Salon--Lybba doesn't seem interested; Leslie has pneumonia
Jun 9, [1931] - To: Jane - From: Posie - Subjects: Posie's eyes; Bob and Mary Sherwood staying in Beverly Hills with Geoffrey Kerr and June Walker (her play ended); filming Waterloo Bridge; Lunts in Hollywood for movie Private Lives
Jun 30, [1931] - To: Jane - From: Lydia - Subjects: Ros in Cleveland; Wee to go to Gouve's graduation from Harvard; Bob and Mary Sherwood; Florence and Langers; Lydia paints Hopey Proctor; Wilfrid's Pope portrait
[Jul 1, 1931?] - To: [Lydia] - From: S [Susie] - Subjects: the Kerrs' baby; Susie to go to Cannes; Paris concert; little Nelly's recovery; poor Nite; house hunt
Jul 2, [1931?] - To: Jane - From: Lydia - Subject: Arthur Jr. lost his job?; Lydia can finally do her own hair--the operation; Lydia
May have to sell or rent new studio; no news of Maman
Jul 12, [1931?] - To: Posie - From: Lydia - Subject: Lydia's arm on the mend
Jul 24, 1931 - To: Ros - From: Cornelia - Subject: John's portrait
Jul 26, [1931?] - To: Jane - From: Posie - Subjects: Marga's engagement to Frank Kinnicutt; Mrs. Stewart
Jul 26, [1931?] - To: Jane - From: Posie - Subjects: Temple, Alida and Elizabeth Chapman tried to force Marga to marry when she was 22; Nigel Playfair wants to produce Marching As to War
Jul 30, [1931] - To: Posie - From: Jane (in Cornwall) - Subjects: Marga's engagement; Temple Biddle drove Elizabeth Biddle and her 2 girls from Dartmoor; Bobby Sherwood in England on holiday
Aug 8, [1931?] - To: Jane - From: Lydia - Subjects: House on lake Otsego built by Harry Milliken for Alice Otis, one of the Wardwell girls whose daughter goes to school with Lydia Sherwood; Florence Wardwell is in politics; Mrs. Pell's wedding; tea at Jim Cooper's (married Susan Sage)- Lydia painted his grandson James Fenimore Cooper last spring; Archie bringing June Walker home from California; Connie (Brandon)'s wedding Sep 6; Peggy Cresson and Jean McLane; finished Hopey Proctor; Kobbe tragedy: Tom Hughes died of polio--husband of Mousie, who is expecting
Aug 12, [1931] - To: Jane - From: Posie - Subjects: Lybba reconciled; Geoff Kerr signed with Paramount; June Walker goes to NY; Bobby Sherwood home soon; Henrietta has cancer
Aug 23, 1931 - To: Lydia - From: Jane (in Bergerac, Dordogne) - Subjects: Jane in Brittany since Aug 17; Suse and Mox Kobbe; Juliette Monod; Suzanne Robineaux; Jane did drawing of John and gave it to Kobbe; Jane will go to Cannes
Aug 24, [1931] - To: Jane - From: Posie - Subjects: Marga and Frank's wedding; Wee's 21st birthday; Bobby and Mary Sherwood return; Bobby Sherwood's work with Douglas Fairbanks in Virtuous Knight; Queen's Husband
Aug 25, [1931] - To: Jane - From: Lydia (at Mt. Carmel) - Subjects: Marga and Frank Kinnicutt's wedding; Madie to Tuckanuck with LaFarges
Aug 27, [1931?] - To: Jane - From: Posie - Subjects: Geoffrey Kerr visits and June still in Hollywood; Bob and Mary; Connie Brandon; Geoffrey's play soon in rehearsal; Mrs. Ryerson at Hyde Hall; saw Emperor Jones--opinion of blacks; watercolor of little Mary
Sep 13, 1931 - To: Jane - From: Posie - Subjects: Cynthia in play Reunion in Vienna-- Mr. Miner to direct; Barry Jones says The Queen's Husband will open in October; the Lunts' first talkie The Guardsman; the Johnson Stoddards; Bancel says apartment will be ready Jan 1
Sep 22, [1931] - To: Jane - From: Lydia - Subjects: Marga's wedding (Frank Kinnicutt's brother is Herman); Mousie's baby due; Connie Brandon)'s wedding toMr. Stoddard; Bay's boys; Lunts and Cynthia in Reunion in Vienna; hurricane; old Mr. Judah
Sep 23, [1931] - To: Jane - From: Posie - Subjects: Ros to Canada for golf; Mary Sherwood says rehearsals go well, Lunts love the play; Barry Jones in Queen's Husband; saw Bay at Lenox horse show
[Oct 1931] - To: [Jane] - From: Lydia - Subjects: Mr. French died--his funeral at his studio
Oct 16, [1931] - To: Jane - From: Lydia - Subjects: Lydia's broken arm; Lydia paints Kilborne girl
Oct 25, [1931] - To: Jane - From: Posie - Subjects: Lydia Sherwood is happy at school; Posie's great-aunt's stories of Indians; Bobby's book not successful
Nov 6, 1931 - To: Lydia - From: Posie - Subject: Dorothy Parker quote
Nov 16, 1931 - To: Jane - From: Posie - Subjects: Arthur with Meredith Blagden and Titus Rand (Barbara's husband); Arthur's family to move in with her at 216 E 70th Street on Feb 1; June and Geoff at Christmas--Geoff in movie Once a Lady and was father in Waterloo Bridge; Geoff wrote book Recollections of a Defective Memory; Reunion in Vienna benefit for unemployed--Woollcott wired Bobby Sherwood